Innocence Lost... Courage Found
Journey's End is a war, drama, action film directed by Saul Dibb.
Set in a dugout in Aisne in 1918, a group of British officers, led by the mentally
disintegrating young officer Stanhope, variously await their fate.
Raleigh, played by Asa Butterfield.
Captain Stanhope, played by Sam Claflin.
Osborne, played by Paul Bettany.
Hibbert, played by Tom Sturridge.
Mason, played by Toby Jones.
Trotter, played by Stephen Graham.
Journey's End is a 2017 British war film based on the 1928 play by R.
Written by Simon Reade and directed by Saul Dibb, it was screened in the "Special
Presentations" section at the 2017 Toronto International Film Festival.
The film is the fifth film adaptation of the play, following Journey's End (1930), The
Other Side (1931), Aces High (1976), and Journey's End (1988 BBC TV film).
The film explores themes of army, france, world war i, british army, alcoholism.
The tone is emotional.